http://www.carolinaclutch.com/privacy-statement

Contact Us
Please contact us if you have any questions, see our inventory of OE LuK replacement clutch Kits and Flywheels, Our RPS Carbon Carbon Performance Clutch Kits or our complete line of ACT Performance Clutch Kits
Choose
Vehicle
Select Vehicle
Year
Year201920182017201620152014201320122011201020092008200720062005200420032002200120001999199819971996199519941993199219911990198919881987198619851984198319821981198019791978197719761975197419731972197119701969196819671966196519641963196219611960195919581957195619551954195319481947194619441943194219411940193919381937
Make
Make
Model
Model
Trim
Trim
Engine Type
Eng Type
Engine Size
Eng Size
Filter Catalog
Privacy Statement
We take your privacy very seriously. The following principles apply to the personally identifying information we ask for and that you provide. "Personally identifying information" is information that individually identifies you, such as your name, physical address or email address.
Data collection
Cookies
Information sharing
Secure shopping and registration
Links
Data collection
Carolina Clutch and Performance, Inc collects limited, non-personally-identifying information your browser makes available whenever you visit a web site. This log information includes your Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your download and in some cases, one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser. We use this information to operate, develop and improve our services.
Some of our services require you to register. Carolina Clutch and Performance, Inc asks you for some personal information in order to create an account (typically your name, email address, physical address, and phone number) and we will use that information to provide the service. For certain services, such as our Online Shop, we may request credit card or other payment information, which is not permanently stored on our servers, but is kept temporarily in memory on our servers while we are negotiating the transaction with our payment processor. We never store your full credit card number, or any part of your card security code, on our servers.
When we require personally identifying information, we will inform you about the types of information we collect and how we use it. We hope this will help you make an informed decision about sharing your personal information with us.
Cookies
To enhance your experience with our site, some of our web pages use "cookies." Cookies are small text files we place in your computer's browser to store your preferences. Cookies, by themselves, do not tell us your e-mail address or other personally identifiable information unless you choose to provide this information to us by, for example, registering at our site. However, once you choose to furnish the site with personally identifiable information, this information may be linked to the data stored in the cookie.
We use cookies to understand site usage and to improve the content and offerings on our site. For example, we may use cookies to personalize your experience at our web pages (e.g. to recognize you by name when you return to our site). We also may use cookies to offer you products, programs, or services.
Information sharing
We do not rent or sell your personally identifying information to other companies or individuals, unless we have your consent. We may share such information in any of the following limited circumstances:
We have your consent.
We provide such information to trusted businesses or persons for the sole purpose of processing personally identifying information on our behalf. When this is done, it is subject to agreements that oblige those parties to process such information only on our instructions and in compliance with this Privacy Policy and appropriate confidentiality and security measures.
We conclude that we are required by law or have a good faith belief that access, preservation, or disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary to protect the rights, property, or safety of Carolina Clutch and Performance, Inc, its users, or the public.
In the event of a transfer of ownership of Carolina Clutch and Performance, Inc (including any publications), such as acquisition by or merger with another company, we will provide notice before any personally identifying information is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.
We may share anonymous, aggregated information with others. Examples of this include the number of users who downloaded a specific product or the number of users clicked on a particular advertisement.
Information security
We take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure, or destruction of data. We restrict access to your personally identifying information to employees who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our services. We provide mechanisms for updating and correcting your personally identifying information for many of our services. You may send an e-mail or letter to the following e-mail or street address requesting access to or correction of your personally identifiable information:
Carolina Clutch and Performance, Inc POB 1651
5932 Wilkinson Blvd
Belmont, NC 28012
Phone: (704) 825-4143
Fax: (704) 825-4145
E-mail: info@carolinaclutch.com
Warranties and returns: info@carolinaclutch.com
Secure shopping and registration guarantee
The purchase and registration areas of our site (Online Shop) are secure. This means that any information you send us is protected by encryption to prevent unauthorized access to your information. The secure site is indicated in the URL with the use of "https://" (visible in the address bar of your web browser), and often reflected at the bottom or address bar of your browser window with a lock or key graphic.
Links
Any links to external web sites may be developed by people over whom Carolina Clutch and Performance, Inc exercises no control. These other sites may place their own cookies on your computer, collect data, or solicit personal information.
Carolina Clutch and Performance, Inc may present links in a format that enables us to understand whether they have been followed. We use this information to understand and improve the quality of our products and web site. For instance, this data helps us determine how popular a product is and if there is anything we can do to improve on it.
